hoverzoom.net 2015-12-30

# Hover Zoom Privacy Policy

Hover Zoom respects your privacy as a user and makes every effort to be transparent. Please read our privacy policy below in order to understand what Hover Zoom can and cannot do with data it collects.

Any data collection mentionned in this Privacy Policy can be disabled by unchecking "Enable anonymous usage statistics" in the options page.

### Collection and Use of Usage Data

When users access or use Hover Zoom, certain browsing behavior information is collected, stored, and then used on an aggregated basis such that no individual is identifiable. The data collected includes, but is not limited to: IP address, unique identifier number, user agent, and webpage URLs visited. We may share with and sell this data to third parties who provide research and analytics services, such as measuring online consumer trends and usage.

### User Consent

When you use Hover Zoom and leave "Enable anonymous usage statistics" checked in the options page, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We know that you care about how your information is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected when you make use of Hover Zoom, as well as how the information will be used. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. Please check back periodically for the most updated version of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Hover Zoom after this Privacy Policy has been amended shall be deemed as your continued acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended.

### Use and disclosure

We may share and sell non-personally identifiable or aggregated information with third parties to provide research and analytics services, such as measuring website usage, performance and ecommerce activity, and analyzing consumer interests, demographics, and market trends.

### Information Collected

#### Browsing History and IP

We may collect results of your browsing preferences and habits, we collect information regarding your use of Hover Zoom including URLs and Statistical Information of websites you may be browsing while Hover Zoom is installed. Hover Zoom continuously and automatically transfers such information to our partners' systems and is being collected in an aggregated manner.

While we would never collect any personal Information submitted to such websites, note that we may save aggregated Browsing History.

Hover Zoom may collect IP addresses, which while identifying a device connected to the Internet, and its general location, are in themselves anonymous and contain no information regarding the identity of the ultimate person using the device – such identity is known solely to your ISP.

Moreover, IP addresses assigned by ISPs are generally dynamic and subject to frequent change – static IP addresses are generally assigned only at subscriber’s specific request and frequently require an additional fee.

In case you do not want Hover Zoom to collect the foregoing information, you should uncheck "Enable anonymous usage statistics" in the options page. Alternatively, you can uninstall Hover Zoom or disable Hover Zoom through your browser’s settings.

#### Non Personal Information

Non-Personal Information will be used to ensure the operation, improve, modify, cancel, enrich or adjust of Hover Zoom.

We reserve the right to use, disclose, and\or transfer (for business purpose or otherwise) Non-Personal Information (in the collected form) to third parties and enable them to use Non-Personal information, including, inter alia, potential and actual advertisers, sponsors, business partners, investors, affiliates and consultants at our sole discretion.

#### Personal Information

We never collect any information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address and other ("Personal Information") unless such information is actively provided to us by you.

We will not disclose your Personal Information to any third party, unless:

  * We are required to do so as part of any legal proceedings conducted between you and our extension.
  * We are required to do so by court order.
  * In case the activity of Hover Zoom is transferred to a third party, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms.

#### Statistical Information

Google Analytics is used to collect and aggregate non-identifying information regarding users use of Hover Zoom. Information about this data collection can be found in [Google's privacy policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Use By Children

We do not offer Hover Zoom for use by children. If you are under 18, you may not use Hover Zoom without involvement of a parent or a guardian. We do not knowingly collect information from, and/or about children.

### Product Updates

Hover Zoom performs regular checks for product updates on our servers and may download such updates when needed.

Home
